<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Important, used in manifest -->

    <string name="app_name">DSO Planner Basic</string>
    <string name="about_title">DSO Planner Basic</string>
    <string name="dso_planner">DSO Planner Basic</string>
    <string name="quick_start_guide"><b>Quick Start Guide</b>\nThe application supports two approaches to object selection. The easier way is to turn on NgcIc Star Chart object layer and set limiting magnitude for each layer and field of view (FOV). All objects whose magnitude is below limiting will then be shown on \"Star Chart\". Besides limiting magnitude you could also filter NgcIc layer by object types.\n\nThe second approach is to look through several databases for objects to be observed using various filters (\"Object Selection\"), prepare observation list and get its objects on \"Star Chart\" automatically.\n\nYou could use each approach separately or combine them. For separate use turn off object layers and fill the current observation list, or vice versa turn on object layers and clear current observation list. For combination both turn on object layers and fill the current observation list.\n\n<b>Star Chart</b>\n\"Star Chart\" shows stars and objects from the selected layers and ALL objects from the current observation list. For each FOV and layer you could adjust limiting magnitude to raise/diminish the number of stars/objects that you see on the screen.\n\nStar Chart is highly customisable, there are many options in \"Star Chart Settings\" that help you adjust it to your needs.\n\nBy default, \"Star Chart\" depicts preinstalled Digitized Sky Survey (DSS) images and their contours. They are not objects in a usual sense, rather consider them belonging to DSS image layer. To download DSS image of any object/sky portion select an object or a star and go to Menu/DSS. Remove DSS image or download image of adjacent area with two long touches on existing image/adjacent area.\n\n<b>Object Selection</b>\nTo search for objects go to \"Object Selection\" screen. Press \"Select\" button. Select object types, catalogs, minimum dimension, visibility filter (object visibility, maximum magnitude) and minimum altitude.\n\nReturn back. Select your geographic location, observation time range and sky conditions. Return back and press \"Update\" button. Here you are with a list of objects.\n\nPress on the object to see its location on \"Star Chart\". Long tap on the list and select \"Add (all) to observation list\" to add object(s) to the current observation list (and they become visible on Star Chart).\n\n<b>Observations Lists</b>\n\nThere are four observation lists. The current one is displayed in \"Observations Lists\" screen, its objects are shown on \"Star Chart\". Change the current observation list in Menu. Menu provides for other observation list operations (sorting, note matching, etc.) as well.\n\n<b>Manual</b>\ndsoplanner.com/files/DSO_Planner_User_Manual.pdf</string>

</resources>
